http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Racing+Stripes&y=2005&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Racing Stripes" year="2005" rated="PG" released="14 Jan 2005" runtime="102 min" genre="Adventure, Comedy, Drama" director="Frederik Du Chau" writer="David Schmidt (story), Steven P. Wegner (story), Kirk De Micco (story), Frederik Du Chau (story), David Schmidt (screenplay)" actors="Bruce Greenwood, Hayden Panettiere, Caspar Poyck, Gary Bullock" plot="In the middle of a raging thunderstorm, a traveling circus accidentally leaves behind some very precious cargo--a baby zebra. The gangly little foal is rescued by horse farmer Nolan Walsh, who takes him home to his young daughter Channing. Once a champion thoroughbred trainer, Walsh has given up horse training for a quiet life with Channing on their modest Kentucky farm. The little zebra, or &amp;quot;Stripes,&amp;quot; as Channing calls him, is soon introduced to the farm's misfit troupe of barnyard residents, led by a cranky Shetland Pony named Tucker and Franny, a wise old goat who keeps the family in line. The group is joined by Goose, a deranged big-city pelican who's hiding out in the sticks until the heat dies down in Jersey. The un-aptly named bloodhound Lightening keeps a lazy eye on goings-on at the farm - in between naps. The Walsh farm borders the Turfway Racetrack, where highly skilled thoroughbreds compete for horse racing's top honor, the ultra-prestigious Kentucky Crown. From the first moment Stripes lays eyes on the track, he's hooked--he knows that if he could just get the chance, he could leave all those other horses in the dust. What he doesn't know is--he's not exactly a horse. But with characteristic zeal, he devotes himself to training for the big time, with a little help from Tucker, who has coached a host of champion racehorses in the past." language="English" country="USA" awards="3 nominations." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE0NDA2MTQwM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzYxNDcyMQ@@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="43" imdbRating="5.2" imdbVotes="13,344" imdbID="tt0376105" type="movie"/></root>