http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=The+Book+Thief&y=2013&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="The Book Thief" year="2013" rated="PG-13" released="27 Nov 2013" runtime="131 min" genre="Drama, War" director="Brian Percival" writer="Markus Zusak (based on the novel by), Michael Petroni (screenplay)" actors="Roger Allam, Sophie Nélisse, Heike Makatsch, Julian Lehmann" plot="In 1938, the young girl Liesel Meminger is traveling by train with her mother and her younger brother when he dies. Her mother buries the boy in a cemetery by the tracks and Liesel picks up a book, &amp;quot;The Gravediggers Handbook&amp;quot;, which was left on the grave of her brother and brings it with her. Liesel is delivered to a foster family in a small town and later she learns that her mother left her because she is a communist. Her stepmother, Rosa Hubermann, is a rude but caring woman and her stepfather, Hans Hubermann, is a simple kind-hearted man. Liesel befriends her next door neighbor, the boy Rudy Steiner, and they go together to the school. When Hans discovers that Liesel cannot read, he teaches her using her book and Liesel becomes an obsessed reader. During a Nazi speech where the locals are forced to burn books in a bonfire, Liesel recovers one book for her and the Mayor's wife Ilsa Hermann witnesses her action. Meanwhile Hans hides the Jewish Max Vandenburg, who is the son of a deceased friend that saved his life in the war, in the basement of his house and Liesel becomes his friend. One day, Rosa asks Liesel to deliver laundry to the Mayor and Ilsa invites Liesel to go to her library and tells that she can visit her to read whenever she wants. But in times of war there are many threats and the lives of Liesel, her family and friends will never be the same." language="English, German" country="USA, Germany" awards="Nominated for 1 Oscar. Another 8 wins &amp; 14 nominations." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTE3NzkyMjAyNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDc5MTE0MDE@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="53" imdbRating="7.6" imdbVotes="107,159" imdbID="tt0816442" type="movie"/></root>