http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=The+In-Laws&y=2003&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="The In-Laws" year="2003" rated="PG-13" released="23 May 2003" runtime="98 min" genre="Action, Comedy, Thriller" director="Andrew Fleming" writer="Andrew Bergman (screenplay), Nat Mauldin (screenplay), Ed Solomon (screenplay)" actors="Michael Douglas, Michael Bodnar, Vladimir Radian, Robin Tunney" plot="In four days, Jerry Peyser and Steve Tobias will become in-laws when their respective offspring, Melissa Peyser and Mark Tobias, get married. Married Jerry is a Chicago area podiatrist. He is risk averse to an extreme, afraid of heights including being in tall buildings and flying, even watching airline commercials. He is also extremely controlling, having organized the lavish wedding against the simple affair Melissa had envisioned. He is aggravated that he has not yet met Steve, who has missed one family function after another. Divorced Steve is a photocopy machine salesman... or so Mark says. In reality, Steve is a deep undercover CIA field agent, something that Mark knows but is unable to divulge to anyone, even Tracy and her family. His work, which has always overtaken his life, is the reason Steve has missed all these family events. Steve is unwilling to hand over reigns of his cases to his junior partner, the capable Angela Harris. Steve finally meets the Peysers, which Steve manipulates into an undercover work dinner. Steve's current mission involves setting up the sale of twenty year old runaway &amp;quot;Olga&amp;quot; to a French arms dealer, violent Jean-Pierre Thibodoux, which is purely a cover to obtain information clandestinely from Thibodoux. Jerry inadvertently gets embroiled in Steve's case when he overhears the beginning of the deal going down. Jerry does not believe Steve to be one of &amp;quot;the good guys&amp;quot;, especially as he learns that the FBI is after Steve, who they believe has become a rogue agent. This belief may affect not only their time together, but their lives and whether Melissa and Mark will get married. Thrown into the mix is Mark's mother/Steve's ex-wife, Judy Tobias, who hates almost everything about her ex-husband except one thing..." language="English, French, Mandarin" country="USA, Germany, Canada" awards="N/A" poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ1MDQ0MTA3NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwMDQxNDA3._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="46" imdbRating="5.7" imdbVotes="14,422" imdbID="tt0314786" type="movie"/></root>