http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Little+Giants&y=1994&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Little Giants" year="1994" rated="PG" released="14 Oct 1994" runtime="107 min" genre="Comedy, Family, Sport" director="Duwayne Dunham" writer="James Ferguson (story), Robert Shallcross (story), James Ferguson (screenplay), Robert Shallcross (screenplay), Tommy Swerdlow (screenplay), Michael Goldberg (screenplay)" actors="Rick Moranis, Ed O'Neill, Shawna Waldron, Devon Sawa" plot="In Urbania, Ohio, snobby ex-football star Kevin O'Shea conducts try-outs for the town's Peewee football team, the Urbania Cowboys, which will compete for a chance at the state Peewee football playoffs. Kevin slights his younger brother Danny O'Shea by rejecting Danny's daughter Becky &amp;quot;Icebox&amp;quot; O'Shea, who is a good player. Kevin rejected her simply because she's a girl. Becky and some of her friends, boys who were also rejected, get the idea to start up their own team, to be coached by Danny. After Kevin tries to put a stop to that plan, Danny gets Kevin to agree to a game to decide which team will represent Urbania, because each town is allowed only one team. Danny and Becky scour the town in search of willing players, and they gather a crew of kids who have limited skills and no team spirit. They luck out when Becky discovers Junior Floyd expertly passing rolls of toilet paper right into a shopping cart at the supermarket, as though he's passing a football. With Becky and Junior on board, the new team, the Giants, has a chance to make a good showing, and they begin their training. But low morale continually threatens to break up the team. A chance visit by former NFL football coach John Madden and four NFL football stars -- Steve Entman, Bruce Smith, Emmitt Smith, and Tim Brown -- leaves the team with several tips on how to create an advantage. Becky develops a crush on Junior Floyd, and she's jealous when her cheerleader cousin Debbie flirts with Junior. Becky decides to compete for Junior on equal terms, so she puts on make-up and a cheerleader outfit, joining the cheerleaders and abandoning the team. But the Cowboys will be coming into the game with a vicious new player named Spike Hammersmith. Will Becky be there for the team if they need her?" language="English" country="USA" awards="N/A" poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTBlNGFmNTktZGJlZi00ZWNkLWI0MGItNjhhNjQyNWM1MmVlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="N/A" imdbRating="6.3" imdbVotes="20,825" imdbID="tt0110364" type="movie"/></root>