http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Show+Boat&y=1951&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Show Boat" year="1951" rated="APPROVED" released="24 Sep 1951" runtime="108 min" genre="Drama, Family, Musical" director="George Sidney" writer="John Lee Mahin (screen play), Jerome Kern (based on the immortal musical play &amp;quot;Show Boat&amp;quot; by), Oscar Hammerstein II (based on the immortal musical play &amp;quot;Show Boat&amp;quot; by), Edna Ferber (from novel)" actors="Kathryn Grayson, Ava Gardner, Howard Keel, Joe E. Brown" plot="The &amp;quot;Cotton Blossom&amp;quot;, owned by the Hawk family, is the show boat where everyone comes for great musical entertainment down south. Julie LaVerne and her husband are the stars of the show. After a snitch on board calls the local police that Julie (who's half- African-American) is married to a white man, they are forced to leave the show boat. The reason being, that down south interracial marriages are forbidden. Magnolia Hawk, Captain Andy Hawks' daughter, becomes the new show boat attraction and her leading man is Gaylord Ravenal, a gambler. The two instantly fall in love, and marry, without Parthy Hawks approval. Magnolia and Gaylord leave the &amp;quot;Cotton Blossom&amp;quot; for a whirl-wind honeymoon and to live in a Pl: fantasy world. Magnolia soon faces reality quickly, that gambling means more to Gaylord than anything else. Magnolia confronts Gaylord and after he gambles away their fortune he leaves her - not knowing she is pregnant. Magnolia is left penniless and pregnant, and is left to fend for herself, and make a new start." language="English" country="USA" awards="Nominated for 2 Oscars. Another 1 win &amp; 2 nominations." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmI4MGE2OGItNWU0ZS00NjczLTkwM2MtMzAyNDYxYTJkNjA2L2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjQzNDI3NzY@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="N/A" imdbRating="7.0" imdbVotes="3,747" imdbID="tt0044030" type="movie"/></root>