http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Movie+43&y=2013&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Movie 43" year="2013" rated="R" released="25 Jan 2013" runtime="94 min" genre="Comedy, Romance" director="Elizabeth Banks, Steven Brill, Steve Carr, Rusty Cundieff, James Duffy, Griffin Dunne, Peter Farrelly, Patrik Forsberg, Will Graham, James Gunn, Brett Ratner, Jonathan van Tulleken, Bob Odenkirk" writer="Rocky Russo, Jeremy Sosenko, Ricky Blitt, Rocky Russo (screenplay), Jeremy Sosenko (screenplay), Bill O'Malley (story), Will Graham, Jack Kukoda, Rocky Russo, Jeremy Sosenko, Matt Portenoy, Rocky Russo (screenplay), Jeremy Sosenko (screenplay), Claes Kjellstrom (story), Jonas Wittenmark (story), Tobias Carlson (story), Will Carlough, Jonathan van Tulleken, Elizabeth Shapiro, Patrik Forsberg, Olle Sarri, Jacob Fleisher, Greg Pritikin, Rocky Russo, Jeremy Sosenko, James Gunn" actors="Dennis Quaid, Greg Kinnear, Common, Charlie Saxton" plot="Ineffectual, 'has-been' film-maker (Dennis Quaid) swindles his way into an interview with a film executive (Greg Kinnear) in order to pitch an outrageous and controversial comedy manuscript. After pitching the first of his thirteen offbeat fables, the dejected artist forces the rest of his disjointed allegory on the executive at gunpoint. He tells stories of a woman on a blind date with a man who has testicles growing from his neck, in another a smitten woman offers her neck to her boyfriend to 'poop' on -as a sign of commitment and love. In yet another two parents take home-schooling to a whole new level of indecency, striving to give their isolated teenage son all the 'regular' torment and humiliation of puberty by bullying, peer-pressuring and even seducing him themselves. An off-beat, elephant-in-the-room type film." language="English" country="USA" awards="4 wins &amp; 5 nominations." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg4NzQ3NDM1Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjEzMjM3OA@@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="18" imdbRating="4.3" imdbVotes="84,250" imdbID="tt1333125" type="movie"/></root>