http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Trainwreck&y=2015&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Trainwreck" year="2015" rated="R" released="17 Jul 2015" runtime="125 min" genre="Comedy, Drama, Romance" director="Judd Apatow" writer="Amy Schumer" actors="Colin Quinn, Devin Fabry, Carla Oudin, Amy Schumer" plot="Despite having a love/hate relationship with her scoundrel of a father Gordon Townsend, the one thing Amy Townsend has grown up believing from him is that monogamy isn't realistic, he and Amy's mom who broke up due to infidelity when Amy was young. As such, she gets drunk and stoned frequently in her pursuit of indiscriminate sex, with an unstated rule that there is no sleeping over once the sex is over. Her current &amp;quot;boyfriend&amp;quot;, Steven, believes they are exclusive, not knowing that she sleeps with other men. Working at sensationalistic magazine S'nuff under head sensationalist Dianna, Amy is in line for a promotion, she certain to get it if her next story meets Dianna's scrutiny. That story is a profile of sports doctor to the stars, Dr. Aaron Conners, it despite Amy knowing nothing about sports. To Amy's amazement, Aaron wants to date her following their first sexual encounter, his sexual history in terms of quantity which is in extreme contrast to her own. Also to her amazement, she kind of wants to date him, the entire ritual of being the one person in another person's life a foreign concept to her. The road to a happy ending for the two is not guaranteed as their very different sexual histories and very different perspectives on sexual life may make them incompatible despite truly liking each other as people. Ensuring that his man Aaron is happy and doesn't get hurt in the process is someone who seems to take Aaron's personal life even more to heart than he does: LeBron James." language="English" country="Japan, USA" awards="Nominated for 2 Golden Globes. Another 5 wins &amp; 22 nominations." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ4MjgwNTMyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTc1MjI0NDE@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="75" imdbRating="6.3" imdbVotes="107,799" imdbID="tt3152624" type="movie"/></root>