http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Jack+Reacher%3A+Never+Go+Back&y=2016&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Jack Reacher: Never Go Back" year="2016" rated="PG-13" released="21 Oct 2016" runtime="118 min" genre="Action, Adventure, Crime" director="Edward Zwick" writer="Richard Wenk (screenplay), Edward Zwick (screenplay), Marshall Herskovitz (screenplay), Lee Child (book)" actors="Tom Cruise, Cobie Smulders, Aldis Hodge, Danika Yarosh" plot="After accomplishing the assignment of dismantling a human trafficking organization, the former military and drifter Jack Reacher goes to Washington to invite his liaison, Major Susan Turner, to have dinner with him. However, he meets her substitute, Colonel Sam Morgan, who explains that Major Turner has been arrested and accused of espionage. Jack seeks out her veteran lawyer, Colonel Bob Moorcroft, who explains that Major Turner has also been accused of the murders of two soldiers in Afghanistan. Further, he also tells Jack he is being sued, accused by a woman of being the father of her fifteen year-old daughter, Samantha. When Moorcroft is murdered, Jack is accused of being the killer and sent to a prison. He sees that Turner and he have been framed and also that Turner will be killed by two assassins. However, he rescues her and they flee. Soon, they realize that there is a conspiracy involving military people from the army and a government contractor that is a powerful arms dealer. Jack also learns that Samantha is in danger and Turner and he rescue her. They decide to protect her since a skilled assassin is hunting them down while they try to find the motive of the conspiracy. Who can be trusted?" language="English, Ukrainian" country="China, USA" awards="N/A" poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODQ3ODQ3NDI4NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDY1Mzk5OTE@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="47" imdbRating="6.1" imdbVotes="84,451" imdbID="tt3393786" type="movie"/></root>