http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Oh%2C+God%21&y=1977&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Oh, God!" year="1977" rated="PG" released="07 Oct 1977" runtime="98 min" genre="Comedy, Fantasy" director="Carl Reiner" writer="Larry Gelbart (screenplay), Avery Corman (based on the novel by)" actors="John Denver, George Burns, Teri Garr, Donald Pleasence" plot="Married to Bobbie Landers with two preteen children, Adam and Becky Lambert, they living in Tarzana, California, mild manned Jerry Lambert is a hard working assistant manager at a Food World supermarket outlet, he who is always trying to do his best at his job. What is his generally uneventful life takes a turn when he receives a hand delivered note in the mail to attend an interview with God. Believing it a gag from his friend Artie Coogan, Jerry decides to go to the interview based on circumstances which compel him to do so. Based on further circumstances of the interview, Jerry, despite not being a religious person, ultimately does believe that who he meets with - initially only a voice - is indeed God, who eventually does show himself in a physical form to Jerry. God wants Jerry to be his messenger - much like a present day Moses - to pass along to the human race that &amp;quot;he&amp;quot; has provided all the necessary components of a successful existence, and it is up to the human race to do with those components as they believe fit to reach that success. God came at this time because of his disappointment with the current state of the world. He also chose Jerry as his messenger because of Jerry being a decent person. Jerry tries to convey the message as best as he can, but runs into one roadblock after another. Once Jerry does gain a wider audience, he is treated as a crazy person and/or a fanatic, those opinions which affect his and his family's life. Jerry believes he has no other option but to continue to do this job for God despite these negative effects. It may take him getting a meeting with so called experts - theologians - before he is taken seriously, or not, as some of those, such as Reverend Willie Williams, God knows is using religion for their own as opposed to societal benefit." language="English, Spanish" country="USA" awards="Nominated for 1 Oscar. Another 3 wins &amp; 2 nominations." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTM2ODcwNTYxMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTc4MzUxMQ@@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="N/A" imdbRating="6.6" imdbVotes="7,383" imdbID="tt0076489" type="movie"/></root>