http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Pocahontas&y=1995&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Pocahontas" year="1995" rated="G" released="23 Jun 1995" runtime="81 min" genre="Animation, Adventure, Drama" director="Mike Gabriel, Eric Goldberg" writer="Carl Binder, Susannah Grant, Philip LaZebnik, Glen Keane (story), Joe Grant (story), Ralph Zondag (story), Burny Mattinson (story), Ed Gombert (story), Kaan Kalyon (story), Francis Glebas (story), Rob Gibbs (story), Bruce Morris (story), Todd Kurosawa (story), Duncan Marjoribanks (story), Chris Buck (story), Mike Gabriel (based on an idea by), Andrew Chapman (additional story development), Randy Cartwright (additional story development), Will Finn (additional story development), Broose Johnson (additional story development), T. Daniel Hofstedt (additional story development), David Pruiksma (additional story development), Nik Ranieri (additional story development), Vincent DeFrances (additional story development), Tom Mazzocco (additional story development), Don Dougherty (additional story development), Jorgen Klubien (additional story development)" actors="Joe Baker, Christian Bale, Irene Bedard, Billy Connolly" plot="This is the Disney animated tale of the romance between a young American Indian woman named Pocahontas and Capt. John Smith, who journeyed to the New World with other settlers to begin fresh lives. Her powerful father, Chief Powhatan, disapproves of their relationship and wants her to marry a native warrior. Meanwhile, Smith's fellow Englishmen hope to rob the Native Americans of their gold. Can Pocahontas' love for Smith save the day?" language="English, Algonquin" country="USA" awards="Won 2 Oscars. Another 13 wins &amp; 6 nominations." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzc4YzhiN2ItY2Y4NC00YTA0LWEyMjEtNzllNTcxZDdjODhiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTUyMzE4Mzg@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="58" imdbRating="6.7" imdbVotes="130,880" imdbID="tt0114148" type="movie"/></root>