http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=S.O.B.&y=1981&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="S.O.B." year="1981" rated="R" released="01 Jul 1981" runtime="122 min" genre="Comedy, Drama" director="Blake Edwards" writer="Blake Edwards" actors="Julie Andrews, William Holden, Marisa Berenson, Larry Hagman" plot="Felix Farmer is an extremely successful Hollywood producer, whose movies for Capitol Pictures have never lost money,... until now, with his latest, most expensive film to date, Night Wind, ending up being a major flop. The film, starring his popular Academy Award winning actress wife, Sally Miles, who has a G-rated screen image, almost bankrupts the studio. As such, the studio execs turn on Felix, who want to take over creative control of the movie and re-edit it to lessen the damage. It also turns Felix suicidal, his mental state which in turn leads to Sally leaving him and taking their two children with her. As Felix tries and tries again unsuccessfully to kill himself, he finally stumbles upon an idea which gets him out of his depression. He plans to use his and Sally's money to purchase the movie back from the studio, and re-imagine it by adding a few new scenes, to drastically altar it from the G-rated fantasy film it is, to an R-rated sex romp, complete with Sally baring her naked breasts on screen. In doing so, Felix believes it has the potential to become the most popular film to date. A major obstacle in being able to carry out his idea is Sally, who has long protected her good girl screen image. What ends up happening is largely dictated by those around them, from the major players to those on the periphery of their lives, each who is working on his or her own self interest, with even those at the far edge of the periphery having a profound effect on the proceedings." language="English" country="USA" awards="Nominated for 1 Golden Globe. Another 1 win &amp; 3 nominations." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTc4MTRhNzQtMTY3Mi00OGM3LTg1ZjUtMGQyMzEzN2Q2OTUzL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjc1NTYyMjg@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="N/A" imdbRating="6.4" imdbVotes="4,435" imdbID="tt0083015" type="movie"/></root>