http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Digimon%3A+The+Movie&y=2000&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Digimon: The Movie" year="2000" rated="PG" released="06 Oct 2000" runtime="82 min" genre="Animation, Action, Adventure" director="Mamoru Hosoda, Shigeyasu Yamauchi" writer="Akiyoshi Hongo (original concept by), Jeff Nimoy (adaptation), Bob Buchholz (adaptation), Jeff Nimoy (screenplay), Bob Buchholz (screenplay)" actors="Lara Jill Miller, Joshua Seth, Bob Papenbrook, David Lodge" plot="The film is an edited version of three different Japanese short films, which have been combined together. There is narration by a continuing character, Kari. The first segment of the film revolves around the first encounter with a digimon and a fight that occurs between their digimon and another. The two kids, Kari and Tai, raise a fast-growing digimon from an egg to a large, dinosaur-like digimon, which escapes from their house and then has an encounter and a battle with a parrot-like digimon. The second segment mainly involves Tai and another digiDestined friend of his, Izzy. A computer virus sweeps across the internet, effecting a digiEgg, and thus creating an infected digimon. This infected digimon begins to start eating computer information and data, and the two protagonists attempt to stop the digimon, but fail. After the infected digimon manages to get into the American information system and launch two nukes, one at japan and one at Colorado, Tai and Izzy get help from teammates Matt and his little brother T.K. They successfully overcome the infected digimon and prevent the nukes from detonating. The third and final segment involves Kari and T.K., now years older, as they see a kid and two digimon fighting whilst in New York. Kari and T.K decide to follow the child, who turns out to be the creator of the virus, and, after meeting up with friends, they manage to defeat the evil digimon, who turns out to be one of Willis' twin digimon that was affected by the virus following the actions of the second segment. Together they fight against this infected digimon, and destroy the virus that was affecting Willis' digimon." language="English" country="USA, Japan" awards="N/A" poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE2NTAyMjUxMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwOTAwODQ3._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="20" imdbRating="6.0" imdbVotes="5,552" imdbID="tt0259974" type="movie"/></root>