http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Mulan&y=1998&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Mulan" year="1998" rated="G" released="19 Jun 1998" runtime="88 min" genre="Animation, Adventure, Family" director="Tony Bancroft, Barry Cook" writer="Robert D. San Souci (based on a story by), Rita Hsiao (screenplay), Chris Sanders (screenplay), Philip LaZebnik (screenplay), Raymond Singer (screenplay), Eugenia Bostwick-Singer (screenplay), Dean DeBlois (story co-head), John Sanford (story), Chris Williams (story), Tim Hodge (story), Julius Aguimatang (story), Burny Mattinson (story), Lorna Cook (story), Barry Johnson (story), Thom Enriquez (story), Ed Gombert (story), Joe Grant (story), Floyd Norman (story), Linda Woolverton (additional story material), Jodi Ann Johnson (additional story material), Alan Ormsby (additional story material), David Reynolds (additional story material), Don Dougherty (additional story material), Jorgen Klubien (additional story material), Denis Rich (additional story material), Joe Ekers (additional story material), Theodore Newton (additional story material), Larry Scholl (additional story material), Daan Jippes (additional story material), Frank Nissen (additional story material), Jeff Snow (additional story material)" actors="Miguel Ferrer, Harvey Fierstein, Freda Foh Shen, June Foray" plot="This retelling of the old Chinese folktale is about the story of a young Chinese maiden who learns that her weakened and lame father is to be called up into the army in order to fight the invading Huns. Knowing that he would never survive the rigours of war in his state, she decides to disguise herself and join in his place. Unknown to her, her ancestors are aware of this and to prevent it, they order a tiny disgraced dragon, Mushu to join her in order to force her to abandon her plan. He agrees, but when he meets Mulan, he learns that she cannot be dissuaded and so decides to help her in the perilous times ahead." language="English, Mandarin" country="USA" awards="Nominated for 1 Oscar. Another 17 wins &amp; 20 nominations." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODczMTdlYjMtZmNlYS00ZTliLTg1Y2YtZTY5MWM2MTQzMzNiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjc0MzMzNjA@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="71" imdbRating="7.6" imdbVotes="188,743" imdbID="tt0120762" type="movie"/></root>