http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=The+Angry+Birds+Movie&y=2016&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="The Angry Birds Movie" year="2016" rated="PG" released="20 May 2016" runtime="97 min" genre="Animation, Action, Adventure" director="Clay Kaytis, Fergal Reilly" writer="Jon Vitti (screenplay), Mikael Hed (story by), Mikko Pöllä (story by), John Cohen (story by)" actors="Jason Sudeikis, Josh Gad, Danny McBride, Maya Rudolph" plot="In the 3D animated comedy, The Angry Birds Movie, we'll finally find out why the birds are so angry. The movie takes us to an island populated entirely by happy, flightless birds - or almost entirely. In this paradise, Red (Jason Sudeikis, We're the Millers, Horrible Bosses), a bird with a temper problem, speedy Chuck (Josh Gad in his first animated role since Frozen), and the volatile Bomb (Danny McBride, This is the End, Eastbound and Down) have always been outsiders. But when the island is visited by mysterious green piggies, it's up to these unlikely outcasts to figure out what the pigs are up to. Featuring a hilarious, all-star voice cast that includes Bill Hader (Trainwreck, Inside Out), Maya Rudolph (Bridesmaids, Sisters), and Peter Dinklage (Game of Thrones), as well as Kate McKinnon (Saturday Night Live, Ghostbusters), Keegan-Michael Key (Key &amp; Peele), Tony Hale (Veep, Arrested Development), Tituss Burgess (Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt), Ike Barinholtz (Neighbors, Sisters), Hannibal Buress (Daddy's Home, Broad City), Jillian Bell (22 Jump Street), Danielle Brooks (Orange is the New Black), Latin music sensation Romeo Santos, YouTube stars Smosh (Ian Hecox and Anthony Padilla), and country music superstar Blake Shelton, who writes and preforms the original song &amp;quot;Friends,&amp;quot; the Columbia Pictures/Rovio Entertainment film is directed by Fergal Reilly and Clay Kaytis and produced by John Cohen and Catherine Winder. The screenplay is by Jon Vitti, and the film is executive produced by Mikael Hed and David Maisel." language="English" country="Finland, USA" awards="6 nominations." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY3MjU0NDA0OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTc0MTU3OTE@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="43" imdbRating="6.3" imdbVotes="57,004" imdbID="tt1985949" type="movie"/></root>