http://www.omdbapi.com/?t=Fantasia&y=1940&plot=full&r=xml&apikey=328708c2<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><root response="True"><movie title="Fantasia" year="1940" rated="G" released="25 Dec 1940" runtime="125 min" genre="Animation, Family, Fantasy" director="James Algar, Samuel Armstrong, Ford Beebe Jr., Norman Ferguson, Jim Handley, T. Hee, Wilfred Jackson, Hamilton Luske, Bill Roberts, Paul Satterfield, Ben Sharpsteen" writer="Joe Grant (story direction), Dick Huemer (story direction), Lee Blair (story development), Elmer Plummer (story development), Phil Dike (story development), Sylvia Moberly-Holland (story development), Norman Wright (story development), Albert Heath (story development), Bianca Majolie (story development), Graham Heid (story development), Perce Pearce (story development), Carl Fallberg (story development), William Martin (story development and research), Leo Thiele (story development and research), Robert Sterner (story development and research), John McLeish (story development and research), Otto Englander (story development), Webb Smith (story development), Erdman Penner (story development), Joseph Sabo (story development), Bill Peet (story development), Vernon Stallings (story development), Campbell Grant (story development), Arthur Heinemann (story development), Phil Dike (story development)" actors="Leopold Stokowski, Deems Taylor" plot="Disney animators set pictures to Western classical music as Leopold Stokowski conducts the Philadelphia Orchestra. &amp;quot;The Sorcerer's Apprentice&amp;quot; features Mickey Mouse as an aspiring magician who oversteps his limits. &amp;quot;The Rite of Spring&amp;quot; tells the story of evolution, from single-celled animals to the death of the dinosaurs. &amp;quot;Dance of the Hours&amp;quot; is a comic ballet performed by ostriches, hippos, elephants, and alligators. &amp;quot;Night on Bald Mountain&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Ave Maria&amp;quot; set the forces of darkness and light against each other as a devilish revel is interrupted by the coming of a new day." language="English" country="USA" awards="8 wins &amp; 1 nomination." poster="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOGE4ZDQ2YWUtYTIzNi00NTI0LTkxMjQtODBjZjE4NjkxNGI4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SX300.jpg" metascore="N/A" imdbRating="7.8" imdbVotes="75,215" imdbID="tt0032455" type="movie"/></root>